Drawn by a landscape as white as snow,
真っ白な景色にいま誘われて
Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
I'm headed toward an unseen world.
僕は行くよ　まだ見ぬ世界へ
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
I've been traveling while lost
迷子のまま旅していた
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
Under this gray sky.
鼠色の空の下
Nezumiiro no sora no shita
Every day with new maps, stained with my many dreams.
日替わりの地図 いくつもの夢が滲んでいた
Higawari no chizu ikutsumo no yume ga nijindeita
I wonder if someday,
いつかはさ
Itsuka wa sa
Even with these tiny steps of mine,
ちっぽけな僕のこの歩幅でも
Chippoke na boku no kono hohaba demo
I'll be able to travel beyond those clouds.
あの雲の向こうまで行けるかな
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
I put on a bold front.
強がって
Tsuyogatte
End up hurting myself.
キズついた
Kizutsuita
I feel empty inside.
心透かしたように
Kokoro sukashita youni
It's started to rain,
降り出した
Furidashita
And the raindrops
雨粒たちが
Amatsubu tachi ga
Began to repeat their scattered reflections.
乱反射繰り返す
Ranhansha kurikaesu
These straight rays of light
真っ直ぐな光が
Massugu na hikari ga
Start to cross one another.
交差して
Kousa shite
And without telling anyone where they're headed,
行き先も告げぬまま
Yakusaki mo tsugenumama
Across the endless distances,
どこまでも
Doko made mo
They pass through all matter.
突き抜ける
Tsukinukeru
I burn these faint afterimages onto my eyes.
淡い残像　両目に焼きつけて
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakitsukete
Under this sky,
この空の下
Kono sora no shita
Wherever I am,
どんなとこにいても
Donna toko ni itemo
I should be able to reach
届くはずなんだ
Todoku hazu nanda
The unseen world.
まだ見ぬ世界へ
Mada minu sekai e
Geez, you still haven't had a bite?
やれやれ　またか
You're an important human sacrifice candidate.
あんたは大事な人柱候補なんだ
We need you to stay healthy.
元気でいてくれなきゃ困るんだよ
Are you listening, Doctor Marcoh?
ねえ　ドクター·マルコー
I've been thinking for some time...
ずっと　考えていた
人柱とはなんなのか
...as to what you mean by "human sacrifice"...
...and about what you are trying to make me do...
お前たちは私に　何をさせようとしているのか
今お前たちがやっているのは
What you are trying to do right now...
...is to create a giant transmutation circle, using this country and its people.
この国と国民すべてを利用して
巨大な錬成陣を作ること
And the purpose of that...
そしてそれは　賢者の石を作るためのもの
...is to create a philosopher's stone. Am I right?
違うか
You're close. On the right track, at least.
惜しい　でもいい線いってる
On the right track?
いい線
So, what are you going to do?
で　どうすんの
If you're not going to help us out, we'll destroy that village.
協力しないってんなら　あの村消しちゃうよ
ラストから聞いてるよ
I heard from Lust.
You'll lend us a hand as long as we promise to leave that village alone, right?
あの村に手を出さないかわりに　協力するってね
What are you going to do?
どうする
Will you help us out and kill everyone in this country?
協力して国民全部滅ぼす
Or will you refuse and let everyone in that village die?
協力しないで　あの村の人間全部消しちゃう
Such a fool.
バカだなぁ
By sacrificing something minor,
you'd be able to save something major.
小を切り捨てりゃ大は助かる
It's a simple concept if you just think about it.
少し考えりゃ分かることなのにさ
まあ　もっともそれがあんたたち人間ってやつだ
Well, I guess that's what makes you guys human.
理屈より情が先に立つ
Emotion always gets in the way of logic.
It was the same way with that guy I killed.
いつか殺した男もそうだった
When I transformed into his wife, he couldn't fight back and lost his chance to get me.
ヤツの女房に化けてみせたら　手を出せなくて
逆転のカードを逃した
It's really helpful to us that you humans are so vulnerable.
つけいりやすくて助かるよ　人間
Seems to me you're really struggling against these humans,
人間相手に随分手こずっているじゃないですか　ラース
Wrath.
To let Scar get away and even have Gluttony captured is unlike you.
スカーに逃げられ　グラトニーまで連れ去られるとは
君らしくもない
ああ　そうだな
Yes, you're right.
You look happy.
うれしそうですね
I won't deny that.
否定はせんよ
少し　楽しい
I'm having fun.
６０年生きてきて　こうして今国のトップに立っている
I've lived for sixty years, and now, I stand at the top of this country.
All according to Father's plan.
すべて父上の予定どおりに
However...
ところが
マスタング大佐にエルリック兄弟　そして
Colonel Mustang, the Elric brothers,
and the ones who come from a foreign land.
外の国から来た者たち
老獪な我々がいいようにかき回されている
We, the wise ones, are being thrown into complete disarray.
It may just be it's almost time for the young ones to take over the generation, Pride.
若者の時代がすぐそこまで来ているのかもしれんぞ
プライド
Wrath, you've interacted with humans for far too long.
ラース　君は長く人間と接しすぎた
That may be true.
そうかもしれん
I want you to remember what exactly we are.
我々がどういう存在なのか忘れないでいただきたい
今の反逆とも取れる発言は
I won't report to Father that earlier statement, which could be interpreted as treachery.
父上には報告しないでおきましょう
More importantly, we need to rescue Gluttony.
それより　グラトニーを
心配ない
There's no need to worry about that.
I have a vague idea of their location based on information I received from the military police.
憲兵隊の情報からおよその場所はつかんでいる
What is this...
何これ
Colonel! Where are you?!
大佐　どこですか
止まれ　中尉
Stop! Lieutenant!
Colonel!
大佐
Lieutenant...
中尉
挑発するな　そいつの狙いは私だ
Don't provoke him!
He's only after me!
Mustang!!!
マスタング
ランファン　ここから出るぞ
Lan Fan! We're getting out of here!
何があったのですか
What... happened?
The monster was keeping another monster inside its belly!
怪物が　腹の中に怪物を飼っていた
周りをばっくり飲み込みやがった
It swallowed everything around him!
こんなものまで作り出すのか　錬金術は
So even something like this is created...
...by alchemy...
There's no other choice. I'll have to kill him.
しかたない　倒させてもらおう
W-Wait, we were finally able to capture a Homunculus!
ちょっ　せっかく捕まえた人造人間だよ
Staying alive is more important.
生き残るのが優先だ
Also, he knows our names and our appearances.
それに　我々の顔と名を覚えられた
There's no reason to let him go alive!
こいつを生かして帰す理由がない
He swallowed...
炎を…
...the fire?
飲んだ
You really are useless, aren't you?!
使えねぇな
だったら　君がなんとかしてみせろ
Then why don't you try to do something about it?!
More like, stop following us! He's only after you, Colonel!
っていうかついてこないでよ
あいつが狙ってるのは大佐だよ
あそこへ逃げ込め　散開
Run into the bushes! Spread out!
Dammit... talk about bad timing...
くそっ　こんなときに
Hurry up, kid!
早くしろ　坊主
急げ　こんな所に長居は無用だ
Hurry! There's no reason to stay here any longer!
But Ed and the others are still...
まだエドたちが
知るか
Not my problem!
オレは ただの一般人だ
I'm just a civilian.
こんな訳の分からん戦いに巻き込まれて死んでたまるか
Getting dragged into some ridiculous battle like this and dying doesn't sound too great to me!
Dammit!
畜生
What's taking them so long?!
あいつら何もたもたしてやがる
ロイ·マスタング
Roy Mustang!!!
No!!!
くそぉ
ダミーに引っ掛かったか
Sounds like he fell for the dummy.
相当頭にきてるみたいだね
He doesn't seem too happy about it either.
Come on, hurry up and go home,
ほら　さっさと帰れ　この役立たず
Mr. Useless.
Lieutenant, you're on this side.
中尉はこっち　ランファンをお願い
Please take care of Lan Fan.
Are you telling me to shamelessly run away in this situation?!
この状況で　おめおめ帰れというのか
You'll just get in the way!
足手まといなんだよ
Please, just leave!
帰って
You're really not helping at all, Colonel.
本気で役に立ってません　大佐
Seriously, this stupid Colonel...
ほんとにこのボケ大佐は
Just do your own job.
いいから自分の仕事をしろ
The fact that the highest ranked man in this country is a Homunculus isn't exactly a problem you can brush aside.
軍のトップが人造人間だなんて
ほうっとける問題じゃねぇだろ
The highest ranked man...
軍のトップって　まさかブラッドレイ大総統が
You don't mean, Führer President Bradley?!
We can talk about this later.
その話はあとだ
乗れ
Hop in!
Looks like there aren't any more empty seats.
Just go ahead without us.
満席だろ　行ってくれ
You idiot!
バカやろう
戦場に　子供だけ残して行けるわけないでしょう
There's no way we can just abandon you kids on the battlefield!
Your opponent is the upper echelon of the army, right?
おたくらの戦う相手は軍上層部だろ
We have to beat some information out of that Gluttony guy.
こっちは　あのグラトニーってヤツから
情報を引き出さなきゃならないんでね
We're going to stay here and fight him.
ここに残って　あいつと戦う
It doesn't matter that we're kids.
子供だからとか　そんなの関係ないよ
We're the ones who came up with this, anyway.
今回の作戦の言いだしっぺはオレたちだ
Thanks for lending us a hand up until now.
ここまで手を貸してくれて　ありがとな
エドワード君
Edward.
Take this with you.
持っていきなさい　使い方は分かるわね
You know how to use it, right?
それは　人を殺す道具だ
That's something used for killing people.
It's something to protect your lives with.
あなたたちの命を守る道具よ
お前の手は　人を殺す手じゃない
Your hands aren't meant for killing people.
Please don't die.
死なないでね
借りとくよ
I'll be borrowing this.
Please, take care of Lan Fan.
ランファンを頼む
Young master...
若　若
Young master!
行こう　行くんだ
Let's go.
Go!
Damn those brats!
くそっ　ガキどもが
Those are the types that end up dying early!
ああいうのが早死にするんだよ
Mustang...
マスタング
ロイ·マスタングはどこだ
Where is Roy Mustang?!
How dare you kill Lust...
よくもラストを…
I won't forgive you!!!
許さんぞぉ
I said we'd fight him, but he's kind of scary.
戦うっつったけど
ぶっちゃけおっかねぇ
He's like a whole new person now...
キャラも変わってるし
どうやって捕まえよう
How are we supposed to capture him?
What's wrong?
どうしたの
犬
A dog?
Stop, Gluttony.
止まれ　グラトニー
I-It talked?!
しゃ　しゃべった
Hey, it's been a while.
やあ　久しぶりだねぇ
鋼のおチビさん
Fullmetal runt.
誰がミジンコゾウリムシどチビか
Who are you calling a flea-sized runt?!
落ち着けよ
Calm down! I just came to pick up Gluttony!
こっちはグラトニーを回収しに来ただけだ
おチビさんとやり合う気は
I have no intentions of fighting mister runt--
７回目
Seventh time!
What are you talking about?!
なんの話だよ
今２回
Twice just now, and fives times back at Research Laboratory 5.
第五研究所の地下で５回
てめぇはオレのことをチビって言った
All told, you've called me a runt seven times!
Don't tell me you forgot!
忘れたとは言わせねぇぞ
You've got such a good memory...
なんだそのピンポイントな記憶力
待て
Wait!
世話焼かせやがって
Giving me so much trouble...
マスタングがいた
I saw Mustang!
ラストの敵
The one who killed Lust!
飲む　飲む　飲んでやる
I'm going to swallow him! Swallow him all up!
大佐はダメだ
You can't do that to the Colonel.
エルリック兄弟もな
Not to the Elric brothers, either.
そんなぁ
No!
さっきも気配を感じたが
I felt it earlier, but...
中に何人いる　人造人間
How many people do you have inside of you, Homunculus?!
お前だな　ラースと斬り結んだという小僧は
So you're the kid who crossed swords with Wrath.
小僧とはなんだオレはシンの国皇帝第１２子
What do you mean by "kid"?!
I'm the 12th Prince of the Xing Dynasty.
その名を
My name is...
飲んでよし
You can swallow him, though.
たははぁ　待て待て待て待てああ
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
なるほど
I see...
僕ら兄弟には手出しできないみたいだね
Looks like you can't do anything to us.
だったら
In that case...
リン　そっちは　任せた
Lin, we'll leave him to you!
ふん　いいだろう
Fine.
見せてもらおうじゃない
Show it to me, then.
ラースと渡り合った腕前ってやつ
Your skills that were enough to challenge Wrath.
ほう　セリムが
Oh, really now?
クラスで１番になったんですって
He got the highest grade in his class.
あなたのことを作文に書いて
On the essay he wrote about you.
あの　読んでもいいですか
Umm... do you mind if I read it here?
今はお行儀が悪いわ
Not at the dinner table, dear.
まあ　いいじゃないか
Come on, what's wrong?
読んで聞かせておくれ
Let's hear it.
はい
Okay!
僕の父は　アメストリス国の大総統です
My father is the Führer President of Amestris.
この国のために一生懸命働いています
He works hard every day for this country.
父の胸にあるのはいつもこの国の人たちのこと
He's always thinking about his people.
みんなが平和に暮らせるように
He's constantly trying to find solutions to problems so that everyone can live in peace.
たくさんの問題に　取り組んでいます
でも　どんなに忙しいときでも
But no matter how busy he is,
he has never forgotten that he has a family.
父は家族を忘れたことはありません
僕を母を愛してくれます
He loves me and my mother.
僕の言葉に　父はいつも耳を傾けてくれる
My father always listens to me.
僕の願いを　いつも聞いてくれる
He always respects my wishes.
そんな父が僕は大好きです
I love my father and everything about him.
ありがとう　セリム
Thank you, Selim.
なかなかやるねぇ
Not bad.
Thank you for the compliment!
お褒めの言葉　どうも
掛かったな
You fell for it!
どうだい
What do you think?
お前ら人間にはできない芸当だろ
It's something you humans can't do, isn't it?
さて　絞め殺されたいか
Now... do you want to be strangled to death?
かみ殺されたいか
Or bitten to death...
それとも切り刻まれる
Or cut to death?
そんじゃ
Actually...
目つぶしとか　せこい手使いやがって
You're cheap, kicking dirt into my eyes...
小さいころから暗殺の危険にさらされ続けてるんでね
There have been many assassination attempts on me, ever since I was little.
反則技も身に付けざるをえなかったんだよ
I've had to learn a few cheap tricks of my own.
どうだい
What do you say? Can't you just give up and turn yourself in?
おとなしく捕まってくれないかな
こっちは不老不死の情報が欲しいだけなんだ
I just want information about immortality.
痛いの嫌だろ
You don't want to get hurt, do you?
くそが
You little shit!
人間風情が見下してんじゃねぇ
You're just a human! Don't be looking down on me!
人間なめるなよ　人造人間
Don't underestimate humans, Homunculus!
よし　捕った
Okay! Got him!
危ないなぁ　もう
That was dangerous, geez...
てめぇ　この
Dammit, you...
お前ら食べちゃダメなの
I'm not allowed to eat you guys!
さっきの糸目が食べたいのに
I want to eat that guy with the thin eyes!
捕まえた
Got him!
おいおい　こっちの邪魔を
Hey now, don't be interfering with--
やっぱり人間だな
You're a human, after all.
今だ　グラトニー
Now, Gluttony!
リン
Lin!
何っ
What?!
くそっ　人柱を飲ませるわけには
Dammit! I can't let him swallow human sacrifices!
兄さん
Brother!
飲んじゃった
I swallowed them.
兄さん　リン
Brother! Lin!
おい　出せよ
Hey, spit him out! Spit out my brother!
兄さんを出せ
無理　飲んじゃった
I can't. I swallowed them.
うそだ　うそだろ
No way...
You're fine, right, Brother?
兄さん
女房やガキが使ってた部屋があるんだが
I've got the rooms my wife and kids used to live in, but if I have too many lights on, the neighbors will get suspicious.
あちこち明かりがついてると近所に怪しまれる
オレのベッドで我慢してくれ
You're going to have to sleep in my bed.
若　若のところへ
I... I have to go to the young master...
バカやろう
Moron!
その体で何ができる
What can you do in that state?!
まだ　帰ってない
He still hasn't returned yet?
分かりました　では直接司令部へ
Got it.
Then I'll be on my way to Headquarters.
はい　失礼します
Yes. Thank you.
行くぞ
We're going.
はい
Roger.
どこへだ
To where?
この際　敵味方をはっきりさせようと思ってね
I need to find out who's on our side and who's not.
ったく　どいつもこいつも
Geez, the whole lot of you...
てめぇの傷も治りきってないのに
You're still going to push yourself,
even though your wound hasn't healed yet?
このうえまだ無茶をしようってのか
大総統が人造人間かもしれんのだ
The Führer President might be a Homunculus.
悠長に構えてはおれまい
I can't just sit around.
それに
Also...
戦場に子供たちだけ残してきた
We just left some kids on the battlefield.
ここで行動しなければ
I'll be setting a bad example as
an adult if I don't take action now!
大人として示しがつかん
何がおかしい
What's so funny?
いえ
Nothing.
大佐に子供扱いされて
I was just thinking about how mad Edward would be if he knew you were treating him like a child.
エドワード君が聞いたら怒るんじゃないかって
あれは君の言葉の受け売りだぞ
I was just repeating your words, you know.
それにしても意外です
But still, I'm amazed.
大佐がこのような大胆な行動に出られるとは
I would have never expected you to take such a bold step.
大胆なものか
It isn't bold at all.
外堀から埋めようというだけだ
I'm just trying to clear the field.
それに
Also...
お前さんを理解して支えてくれる人間を
Have a lot of people who understand and are willing to support you.
一人でも多くつくっておけ
遅まきながら
It's a little late, but I'm going to take his advice.
あいつの忠告に従ってみようと思ってね
栄光の門か魔窟の入り口か
This could either be the gates of glory or an entrance to a den of evil...
中尉はここで待っていろ
You wait here, Lieutenant.
私に万一のことがあったら
If something happens to me, I want you to get out of here.
君だけでも逃げるんだ
嫌です
I refuse.
命令だ
This is an order.
承服できません
I cannot comply.
強情だなぁ
You're quite the stubborn one...
よくご存じかと
You should know that by now.
分かった
Fine.
必ず戻ってくるから待っていろ
I'll definitely come back, so wait for me here.
はっ　ご武運を
Yes, sir! Good luck!
君がロイ·マスタング君か
So you're Roy Mustang, eh?
さっき家内から電話があったよ
I got a call from my wife earlier.
レイブン中将閣下
Lieutenant General Raven! I deeply apologize for not coming to introduce myself to you due to duties.
着任以来
忙しさにかまけて　ご挨拶にも上がらず
あげく　こんな夜分に申し訳ありません
Also, I'm terribly sorry for visiting you at this hour!
かまわんよ
I don't mind.
時にグラマンのたぬきじじいは元気かね
How's the old geezer Grumman doing these days?
相変わらずです
He's doing fine.
チェック
Check.
はぁ　参りました
I'm beat.
これで１１連敗だ
That's eleven losses in a row.
１２だよ
Make that twelve.
まあ　今回はなかなか健闘したがね
Well, I guess you put up a good fight this round.
勝ちを意識してからあとがまずかった
You started to lose your touch right after you started to think you had a chance.
詰めが甘いと
So you're saying I let up?
そう　非情になりきれん
That's right. You're not able to become heartless.
レイブンと同じだ
Just like Raven.
レイブン将軍　セントラルの
General Raven...
From Central?
優秀だが情にもろくてね
He's exceptional, but very soft-hearted.
負傷した部下を自ら助けに行き
There was a case where he ran in to rescue one of his men, who was injured, and ended up disrupting his formation.
陣容を乱すようなところがあった
あれでは駒がいくつあっても足りんわな
If he's like that, he'll need a lot of men on his side.
なっ　なんたる侮辱
W-What an insult!
私はその部下を思う情けを買われて
I was employed at Central because of the way I treat my men!
セントラル勤務になった
辺境のじじいにどうこう言われる筋合いはないわ
A geezer out on the frontier has no right to say that about me!
あっ 失敬
M-My apologies...
お気になさらず
Please don't let it get to you.
ちなみに　このお話にご立腹されたなら
Also, seeing how you got angry at this,
you must be a man of justice.
将軍は今なお正義の人
何かと相談に乗ってくれるだろうと
Lieutenant General Grumman told me I should go to you in times of trouble.
グラマン中将が
はっ　またあのたぬきに一本取られたというわけか
So that sly dog one-upped me again, huh...
おっと　会議の時間だ
Oh, it's almost time for the meeting.
そこまで一緒に行こう
I'll accompany you.
セントラルには慣れたかね
Have you gotten used to Central?
いえ　市民と言葉を交わすように心掛けているのですが
Not quite. I'm trying to bring myself to talk with the people more, but...
市井の噂もバカにできんからな
They've got rumors flying around all over the place, don't they?
しかし　大半は他愛のない話ばかり
But most of those rumors are nonsensical.
スカーが猫に餌をやっていたとか
Something about Scar feeding a cat, immortal beings, and...
死なない人間が現れたとか
大総統が人造人間だ　とか
...something about the Führer President being a Homunculus.
君　ギャグセンスないねぇ
You don't have a great sense of humor, do you?
本当にグラマンの部下だったの
Did you really work under Grumman?
そっち方面は学び損ねました
I guess I didn't pick that up from him.
まあそんなゴシップでも
Well, even gossip like that may end up entertaining everyone.
みんなのお茶うけくらいにはなるだろう
えっ　私などがこのような
Huh? Am I really allowed to...
さて　さっきのジョーク
So, about that earlier joke...
大総統が人造人間だとか
About the Führer President being a Homunculus...
続けたまえ
I'd like you to continue.
どうしたね　マスタング大佐
What's the matter, Colonel Mustang?
私が人造人間だからどうだというのかね
What about me being a Homunculus?
何か問題でも
Is there a problem?
Oh, now I get it, Hughes...
そうかヒューズ
軍がやばいってのは
When you said that the army was in danger...
軍に危機が迫っているというのではなく
...you didn't mean a crisis was approaching the army...
軍そのものがやばいということか
You meant that the army itself was in a crisis.
鋼の　ここは地獄の底だったようだ
Fullmetal.
Looks like I've arrived at the depths of hell.
ここは
Where am I...
血
Blood?
なんだ　なんだよここ
What?
What is this place?
アル　おい　誰かいないのか
Al!
Hey, isn't anyone here?!
ここはどこなんだ
Where the hell am I?!
Let it all out, Let it all out
I don't have to act tough, right?
強がらなくていいんだね
Tsuyogaranakute iindane
The scribbling someone made...
誰かが描いてった
Dareka ga kaitetta
On the wall, of a flower is swaying.
壁の落書きの花が　揺れる
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
No one knows their true selves.
自分らしさなんて, 誰もわからないよ
Jibunrashisa nante dermo wakaranaiyo
Even though we both lose and gain
長い長い道の途中で
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu de
By embarking on this long, long path,
失くしたり, 拾ったり,
Nakushitari hirottari
And though there may be days loneliness strikes and makes us weep...
急に寂しくなって, 泣いちゃう日もあるけど
Kyuu ni samishikunatte naichau hi mo arukedo
Let's transform our tears and pains to stars.
涙も　痛みも　星に変えよう
Namida mo itami mo hoshi ni kaeyou
Let's light a candle to illuminate our tomorrow.
明日を照らす　灯りをともそう
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
And we'll hold our small hands over the fire to create stardust,
小さな手かざして　ふたりで作ろう
Chiisana te kazashite futari de tsukurou
And an eternity that shines so brilliantly.
星屑を　強く光る永遠を探そう
Hoshikuzu wo tsuyoku hikaru eien wo
Farewells may be unavoidable,
さよなら　いつかは来るかもしれない
Sayonara itsuka wa kurukamoshirenai
Yet the seasons continue to change obliviously.
季節はそれでも巡り巡ってく
Kisetsu wa soredemo meguri megutteku
Even if I lose myself, I'll continue to walk...
小さく迷っても　歩いてく
Chiisaku mayottemo aruiteku
Walk by your side.
君と歩いてく
Kimi to aruiteku
That's the only thing I'd like to never change.
それだけは変わらないでいようね
Sore dake wa kawaranaideiyoune
日本語字幕仕上げ：FAYFAY
消えた者を捜すのは
Do people search for the lost because they fear being alone?
孤独に対する恐れなのか
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
だが　たとえ姿が見えなくとも諦めない
But even if he can't see them, he won't give up.
信じているから
Because he believes.
次回　鋼の錬金術師
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
第二十五話
Episode 25, Doorway of Darkness.
闇の扉
私を見るな　この姿を見るな
Don't look at me.
Don't look at this figure.